<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>Context Sensitive Help (CSH) for the FlexForm</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
        	<label index="title.description">Title of the rule set. This is only used in this form to help you keep your rule sets organized.</label>
        	<label index="usergroup.description">Set of backend user groups to which the rule set should be applied.
        		May be left empty.</label>
        	<label index="directories.description">Comma-separated list of directories to be monitored.
        		Example: fileadmin/
        		If empty, the list of directories configured in General tab will be taken into account.
        		
        		Wildcard is supported:
        		fileadmin/*/images/
        		fileadmin/**/images/
        	</label>
			<label index="file_types.description">Comma-separated list of file types to be handled.
				Example: jpg,jpeg,png,tif,tiff
				If empty, the list of file types configured in General tab will be taken into account. 
			</label>
			<label index="threshold.description">Images larger than this value will be resized (allowed units: B|K|M).
				If empty, the threshold configured in General tab will be taken into account.
			</label>
			<label index="max_width.description">Images will be resized up to this maximum width.
				If empty, the maximum width configured in General tab will be taken into account.
			</label>
			<label index="max_height.description">Images will be resized up to this maximum height.
				If empty, the maximum height configured in General tab will be taken into account.
			</label>
			<label index="keep_metadata.description">Either inherit configuration from General settings or explicitly configure wether to keep/strip off color profile and metadata such as EXIF, IPTC and XMP.</label>
			<label index="conversion_mapping.description">Comma-separated list of conversion mapping instructions. This lets you automatically convert the type of the image while resizing it.
				If empty, the conversion mapping instructions configured in Options tab will be taken into account.</label>
        </languageKey>
    </data>
</T3locallang>